I popped Bubble!
Hey! You should not be going around
killing people with your...
Huuuaaghh...
FINGER!
No one tells me what to do!
Oof!
Ha ha!
Dah!
Oh my gosh!
- Pencil: Ahhhhh!
- Snowball: It burns!
Woah!
- Firey: Hueeuhh... Uhh..
- Blocky: Ahhhh!
- Ice Cube: Ahhhh!
- Firey: Ahhhh!
- Blocky: Ahhhh!
- Ice Cube: Ahhhh!
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
Snowball, Bubble, Rocky, and Tennis Ball.
Last episode, you four had the lowest scores.
Go to the Cake at Stake place to see-
who.
Will.
Be.
Eliminated.
You can see it's been remodeled again.
Cool, huh?
Snowball: Oh my god, that is so terrible!
Bubble: Ooh... that... th-that's not good!
Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
Tennis Ball: I hate it! I don't want to see it ever again!
- Snowball: That is the worst thing I ever seen!
- Bubble: Ooh... that... th-that's not good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: I hate it! I don't want to see it ever again!
- Snowball: That is the worst thing I ever seen!
- Bubble: Not good at all! Not good, not good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: I hate it! I don't want to see it ever again!
- Snowball: That...I can't think of anything worse than that!
- Bubble: Not good at all! Not good, not good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: Why would you do something so horrible?
You're supposed to like it.
- Snowball: Oh my god, that is so wonderful!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: I love it! I most certainly want to see it again!
- Snowball: Oh my god, that is so wonderful!
- Bubble: Ooh! That's... that's quite good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: I love it! I most certainly want to see it again!
- Snowball: That is the best thing I have ever seen!
- Bubble: Quite good a lot! Quite good, quite good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: I love it! I most certainly want to see it again!
- Snowball: That is the best thing I have ever seen!
- Bubble: Quite good a lot! Quite good, quite good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: Why would you do
something that’s so wonderful?
- Snowball: That, I mean, I can't think of
anything better than that!
- Bubble: Quite good a lot! Quite good, quite good!
- Rocky: Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!
- Tennis Ball: Why would you do something that’s so wonderful?
That's better. So we got 80 votes.
Announcer:
Bubble, you've gotten 4 votes this time,
quintupling your total number of votes.
You get a cake. It's fish flavored.
More like it is fish!
Announcer:
Rocky, who is at 11 votes, is also quite fishy.
So it looks like another ball is going home.
Announcer:
Snowball, I'm sorry to tell you that
you have been eliminated with a record of 47 votes.
Grrrrr!
Snowball:
NOOOOO...
...OOOOOO!
Announcer:
Tennis Ball, congrats. You are safe, and you get the third fish.
OMG! Bubble and Match, it's so
cool we all got to the final 11!
OMG. It's 'cause, like, we're so totally, like, amazing!
Hueeughhh...
Neuuhheuuhhh!
Hnnnyah!
Ow. Hey! Why did you slap me?
I don't know.
It's just... I'm so used to slapping Coiny.
Now that he's gone, I...
I just have to keep slapping!
Ow! I didn't say anything about kicking!
People, quiet down.
So on this screen, I've ordered you by your current scores.
The Red Zone represents the bottom third.
At the end of this contest, if you're in that
Danger Zone, you will be up for elimination.
But what is this contest?
Wow! Eraser, you're so imp-, that's impatient for short.
OMG, Eraser. You are, like, totally imp.
So the 13th contest, which may be unfortunate for some,
is to find some red balls hidden in random locations.
All you gotta do is to bring one red ball to me.
That's it.
You'll get points depending what
order you bring them in.
Go.
Uhh, is it in here?
No.
That's it, I'm not working with you!
OMG! That bush has 2 red balls!
Match, let's turn them in!
Yeah!
Hey!
We found 2 of the balls!
Pencil, you're the first person to bring me a ball.
Yeah!
Because of that, you get 30 points.
OMG OMG OMG!
Now here's my ball.
Hmm, hold on. I asked for a red ball.
This is a maroon ball.
OMG, seriously?
That will be a 10-point penalty.
I'm sorry.
Go back and find a ball that is actually red.
No, no, no!
Ooh, ooh! Ice Cube, come here!
What's happened?
I found a ball! I rather you get the points though.
You deserve it, for being such a great friend!
Ice Cube, this is a maroon ball. That's a 10-point penalty.
Wha?
Go back, and find a ball that is actually red.
Oh my gosh, Ice Cube, I'm so sorry!
I want revenge!
Hey, robotic talker! So Rocky was having
one of his vomiting spasms,
and he threw up a red ball so here it is!
That's kind of gross.
Announcer:
You, Tennis Ball, are the second
person to bring in a red ball, earning you 20 points.
But I don't think it's possible for
someone to throw up something so large.
Buh... Leh!
I stand corrected. Rocky, third place earns you 15 points.
You find anything?
No, you?
Well, I have an apple.
Geh!
Ball!
Firey, you get fourth place, resulting in 12 points.
This ball better be good.
It is. Being the fifth person to turn in
a red ball, you get 10 points.
OMG, I'm so glad that I'm so out of that Danger Zone.
Yeah, I have myself a ball!
Hueh HAH!
Okay guys, I got myself a ball. What about you?
Like I said, all I have is an apple!
Oh, I found a ball, too!
Great, let's turn them in!
Blocky, you're the sixth person to
turn in a ball, so you get 8 points.
Big mistake, Eraser, that's a maroon ball.
You get a 10-point penalty.
What?!
Maroon and red are the same!
Blocky is so mean!
Really? How so?
He kicked me! I popped!
So he is a murderer!
Okay guys, help me find a ball. It would mean
everything to me, to stay out of that Danger Zone!
Okay, here's a ball.
Leafy, you're number 7.
Announcer:
That gets you 6 points.
Man, that dumb speaker box didn't like my ball.
I have to get another one.
Well, I still have an apple.
Wait, there's a ball hanging from the sky!
It's totally unsuspicious. I think it's perfectly fine!
I think so, too! Go turn it in!
Oh, here's a ball!
Pencil and Match:
Yaaay!
Bubble, you're number 8.
That gets you 4 points.
Yes! I made it out of the Danger Zone!
I got a ball!
Pen, you're number 9.
Announcer:
That gets you 3 points.
So, who are we still waiting for?
Eraser and Ice Cube!
Ice Cube, you're number 10, so you get 2 points.
Come on! I need to get a ball... soon!
Took you long enough.
Well, at least I have it now, right?
Wait, I think that's a maroon ball.
What?!
Actually, I'm not sure. It's too dark to tell.
This is red I know it!
See? Can't you tell? It's red!
Ooh! Cool, fire.
So is it good?
I don't know. Is it?
It is!
Ok, then, Eraser, you're the last person to
bring in a ball.
That gets you only 1 point.
So, these are your current scores.
Announcer:
Match, Ice Cube, Rocky, and Tennis Ball, you have
fallen into the Danger Zone,
Announcer:
so the voting will only be between the 4 of you.
Voters, subscribers, and everyone else out there,
vote for one of these contestants to be
eliminated from the Battle for Dream Island.
Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh! Bleh!